erobertparker.com 2016-10-24

# eRobertParker.com: Privacy

Last modified: June 19, 2003 

At eRobertParker.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. 

COLLECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The personal information we collect from you when you register for our site is used by us in providing our services to you. It will not be sold or provided to any third party unless you specifically approved our doing so at the time you registered. 

If you ever want to review or update your personal information, simply visit the Online Help page. 

CONTROL OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may occasionally allow other companies to provide information to our subscribers about their wine-related products or services. We will never provide any information to these companies other than your email address. We will only do that if you specifically agree to it at the time you register. 

SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

eRobertParker.com strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information will be stored and processed in the United States. 

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your ID and password, so do not share these with others. 

USE OF COOKIES

When you sign onto our Web site it assigns a personal identification number and sends it to your computer in the form of a small text file, called a "cookie." This cookie allows us to monitor your use of our site. This is done only for the purpose of protecting us, and you, should your ID and Password become available to someone other than you. For more details refer to the eRobertParker.com subscription agreement. 

We do not track individuals' use of the site. 

If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the eRobertParker.com Web site, you will not be able to sign on. 

CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT

eRobertParker.com will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this Statement, eRobertParker.com will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site. 

CONTACT INFORMATION

eRobertParker.com welcomes your comments or questions regarding this Statement of Privacy. Send your email to [info@robertparker.com](mailto:info@robertparker.com).
